(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-16T01:55:45.533623",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
私が私の事を愛して
I love myself.
何が悪いのかしら？嫉妬でしょうか？
What's wrong with that? Are you just jealous?
痛いだとか変わってるとか
They say I'm cringey or weird,
届きませんね。そのリプライ
but I'm not listening to those replies.
大好きなお洋服
My favorite clothes,
大好きなお化粧で
my favorite makeup on,
お決まりのハートツイン巻いて
my iconic heart-twintails curled,
お出かけしよう
let's go out!
日傘持って ぼっちだって
With a parasol, even if I'm alone,
幸せだもん！
I'm happy!
Chu！可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute,
生まれてきちゃってごめん
sorry that I was born.
Chu！あざとくてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being calculatingly cute,
気になっちゃうよね？ごめん
sorry that you can't ignore me.
Chu！可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute,
努力しちゃっててごめん
sorry for working hard on myself.
Chu！尊くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being precious,
女子力高くてごめん
sorry for being a girly girl.
ムカついちゃうよね？ざまぁw
It annoys you, right? Serves you right!
貴方は貴方の事だけどうぞ
You do you, so please
私に干渉しないでください
don't interfere with me.
類は友を呼ぶと言うけれど…
They say birds of a feather flock together...
届きませんね。その陰口
I'm not hearing those gossips.
重い厚底ブーツ
Heavy platform boots,
お気に入りのリュックで
my favorite backpack,
崩せない前髪櫛でといて
combing my fringe so it won't ruin,
お出かけしよう
let's go out!
軽い女？ふざけんな
An easy girl? You must be joking,
重すぎるつーの！
I'm way too devoted!
Chu！可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute,
この時代生きててごめん
sorry for living in this era.
Chu！目立っててごめん
Chu! Sorry for standing out,
意識しちゃうよね？ごめん
sorry that you notice me.
Chu！可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute,
自分磨きしててごめん
sorry for working on myself.
Chu！ぶりっ子でごめん
Chu! Sorry for acting cutesy,
処にしちゃっててごめん
sorry for making you fall for me.
ムカついちゃうでしょ？ざまぁ
It annoys you, right? Serves you right!
趣味の違い　変わり者とバカにされても
Even if people mock me for being weird,
曲げたくない　恐ろしくもない
I won't bend, and I'm not scared.
あんたがごとき　自分の味方は自分でありたい
I want to be my own greatest ally,
一番大切にしてあげたい
and cherish myself the most.
理不尽な我慢はさせたくない “それが私”
I refuse to endure unreasonableness—"This is me!"
Chu！可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute,
生まれてきちゃってごめん
sorry that I was born.
Chu！あざとくてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being calculatingly cute,
人生楽しんでごめん
sorry for enjoying my life.
Chu！可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute,
努力しちゃっててごめん
sorry for working hard on myself.
Chu！尊くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being precious,
女子力高くてごめん
sorry for being a girly girl.
ムカついちゃうよね？ざまぁw
It annoys you, right? Serves you right!
Chu！可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute,
生まれてきちゃってごめん
sorry that I was born.
Chu！あざとくてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being calculatingly cute,
気になっちゃうよね？ごめん
sorry that you can't ignore me.
Chu！可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute,
努力しちゃっててごめん
sorry for working hard on myself.
Chu！尊くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being precious,
女子力高くてごめん
sorry for being a girly girl.
ムカついちゃうよね？ざまぁw
It annoys you, right? Serves you right!
おな〜い！みんな〜！おはよ〜！
Hello everyone! Good morning!
ホロライブ4期生の姫森ルーナなのだぁ〜！
It's Hololive 4th Generation's Himemori Luna!
今日はなんと！あなたの3回目の誕生日なのだなや〜！
Today is my 3rd birthday, you see!
みんな見に来てくれてありがと〜！
Thank you everyone for coming to see me!
是非上のハッシュタグ　姫森ルーナ生誕祭2023でたくさんポストしてほしいな〜！
Please post a lot using the hashtag above, #HimemoriLunaBirthday2023!
そして今回のステージもとっても可愛いので一緒に見ていくな〜！
And this concert's stage is super cute, so let's look at it together!
全体的にイングリッシュガーデンを意識してステージをデザインしてもらいました！
We designed the stage with an English garden theme in mind!
今回はCIJ（Cute is Justice）がテーマで、お洒落なお菓子や靴下のデザインなんだね〜！
The theme this time is CIJ (Cute is Justice), featuring stylish sweets and sock designs!
ま、せっかくなのでみんなCIJした……
Well, since we're at it, everyone CIJ-ed...
もっとたくさん使ってほしいのなの！
want you to use lots of them!
そして、
And then...
こっちにいるのは…おるるるるるるるる！
Who's over here? Run, run, run, run, run!
おる？
Wait.
おる、もしかしてルナナイトじゃないのの？ルナナイトー！
Wait, isn't that Lunaknight? Lunaknight!
ルナナイト、お話を聞くのよー！
Lunaknight, pay attention to me!
全然反応しないのね。まじめに仕事して偉いのらルナナイトその調子で頑張ってるのな！
You're not reacting at all! Work properly and be a good Lunaknight, do your best!
そしてこっちにあるのは、キャンディーの噴水とルナナイトの石像なのかな？
And what's over here is candy fountain and Lunaknight statue, right?
これは名誉ルナナイトなのかな？
This is the legendary Lunaknight, right?
おー、すげえかっこいいしかわいいのな。
Oh, super cool and cute, right?
そしてこっちには、お？なんだなんだなんだなんだなんだ？
And over here is... what, what, what, what, what?
あれは神崎ぱぱ！とキャンディーの葉っぱ？なんかその前に…なんか今ちょっとルナナイトも見えましたけど、すごい可愛い葉っぱと、その後ろには…
That's Kanzaki Papa and candy leaves! And right in front... I could see Lunaknight just now, but such cute leaves, and behind that...
お城ー！
Castle!
でっけえルナナイトのお城が見えるのらね！
A huge Lunaknight castle can be seen, right?
ということで、今日はこちらのステージで歌って踊っていくのな！ゲストの皆も呼んでいるので、最後まで楽しんでっていってほしいのなイン！
So, today we're going to sing and dance on this stage! I've also invited guests, so I hope you'll enjoy it all the way to the end, nanoine!
同じ空見上げてるのに
Even though we're looking at the same sky,
風に吹き付けられて似たように凍えるのに
Though the wind blows to the point of freezing,
真剣に歌います。
I'm singing seriously.
聞いてください。粉雪。
Please listen, "Konayuki".
粉雪舞う季節はいつもすれ違い
The season when powder snow dances is always passing us by
人込みに紛れても同じ空見上げてるのに
Even though we're looking at the same sky in a crowd of people
風に吹き飛ばされて似たように凍えるのに
Even though the wind blows us and we freeze as if alike
僕は君のすべてなど知ってはいないだろう
I probably don't know everything about you,
それでも一億人から君を見つけたんだよ
Even so, I found you out of a hundred million people
根拠はないけど本気で思ってるんだ
Though I have no proof, I seriously think so
些細な言い合いもなくて
Without even petty arguments,
同じ時間を生きなくてはいけない
We have to live in the same moment
素直になれないなら喜びも悲しも虚しいだけで
If we can't be honest, happiness and sadness are just empty
粉雪 ねぇ 心まで白く染められたなら
Powder snow, hey, if our hearts were painted white in the snow
二人の孤独を分け合うことができたのかい
Would we have been able to share each other's loneliness?
僕は君の心に耳を押し当ててその声のする方へすっと深くまで
I press my ear against your heart and go deep down to where that voice comes from
降りてゆきたい そこでもう一度会おう
I want to descend so we can meet there once more
分かり合いたいなんて
Wanting to understand each other,
上辺を撫でていたのは僕の方
I was the one caressing the upper side
君のかじかんだ手も握り締めることだけで繋がっていたのに
Even though our cold, numb hands were connected just by holding them tight
粉雪 ねぇ 永遠を前にあまりに脆く
Powder snow, hey, far too frail before eternity
ざらつくアスファルトの上シミになっていくよ
Becoming stains on the rough asphalt
粉雪 ねぇ 時には頼れず心は揺れる
Powder snow, hey, my heart sways without relying on time
それでも僕は君のこと守り続けたい
Even so, I want to keep protecting you
粉雪 ねぇ 心まで白く染められたなら
Powder snow, hey, if our hearts were painted white in the snow
二人の孤独を包んで空に返すから
Wrapping our loneliness and returning it to the sky
寂しさなんて言い聞かせてみても握り締めることだけで
Even if we feel loneliness, holding tight is all I do
粉雪
Powder snow
粉雪舞う季節は いつもすれ違い
In the season when powdery snow dances, we always pass each other by.
人混みに紛れても 同じ空見てるのに
Even if we get lost in the crowd, we're looking at the same sky.
風に吹かれて 似たように凍えるのに
Blown by the wind, freezing just the same,
僕は君の全てなど知ってはいないだろう
I may not know everything about you,
それでも一億人から君を見つけたよ
yet I found you among a hundred million people.
些細な言い合いもなくて 同じ時間を生きていけない
Without even trivial arguments, we can't live the same time together.
粉雪 ねぇ
Powdery snow, hey...
心まで白く染められたなら
If our hearts could be dyed white,
二人の孤独を分け合うことが出来たのかい
could we have shared our loneliness?
僕は君の心に耳を押し当てて その声の方へすっと深くまで
I pressed my ear against your heart, going deep down toward your voice.
下りてゆきたい そこでもう一度会おう
I want to go down and meet you once more there.
上唇を撫でていたのは僕の方
I was the one stroking your upper lip.
君のかじかんだ手も 握りしめることだけで繋がってたのに
Even your numb hands were connected just by holding on tight.
丘を越えて 山を越えて 谷を越えてゆくんだ
Crossing hills, mountains, and valleys, I'll keep going.
川を越えて 海を越えて 空を越えてゆくんだ
Crossing rivers, seas, and skies, I'll keep going.
間違いだらけの毎日も
Even with days full of mistakes,
手と手をつないで 目と目を合わせて どこまでも歩こう
holding hands, looking into each other's eyes, let's walk anywhere.
雨上がりの空 虹を描いて 皆に会いに行くよ
Painting a rainbow in the sky after the rain, I'm going to see everyone.
旅立つの時は 僕でいること
When setting off, being myself,
間違えたっての毎日の道も
even on days when I make mistakes every single day,
目と手をつないで 目と目を合わせて どこまでも歩こう
connecting hands, meeting eyes, let's walk forever.
おサルさんのロンド
The monkey's rondo,
キリンさんのロンド
the giraffe's rondo,
ウサギさんのロンド 気がつけば僕も
the rabbit's rondo, before I knew it, me too.
小犬たちのロンド
The puppies' rondo,
子猫たちのロンド
the kittens' rondo,
小鳥たちのロンド 笑顔で歌うよ
the little birds' rondo, singing with a smile.
朝を越えて 日を越えて 夜を越えてゆくんだ
Crossing morning, day, and night, I keep going.
雲を越えて 時を越えて 星を越えてゆくんだ
Crossing clouds, time, and stars, I keep going.
星空の下に浮かべた涙 皆に会いに行こう
Tears floating under the starry sky, I'm going to see everyone.
大人になればわかるはずなのに 悩みごとばかり増えてゆく
When you become an adult, you should understand, but troubles just keep increasing.
そんなときには空を見上げて
At times like that, look up at the sky,
皆と一緒に歌いながら
while singing together with everyone.
お医者さんのロンド
The doctor's rondo,
大工さんのロンド
the carpenter's rondo,
八百屋さんのロンド 気がつけば僕も
the greengrocer's rondo, before I knew it, me too.
山田さんのロンド
Yamada-san's rondo,
田中さんのロンド
Tanaka-san's rondo,
鈴木さんのロンド 笑顔で歌うよ
Suzuki-san's rondo, singing with a smile.
小人さんのロンド
The dwarf's rondo,
巨人さんのロンド
the giant's rondo,
宇宙人のロンド 気がつけば僕も
the alien's rondo, before I knew it, me too.
寂しがりさんのロンド
The lonely person's rondo,
忘れんぼさんのロンド
the forgetful person's rondo,
照れ屋さんのロンド 笑顔で歌うよ
the shy person's rondo, singing with a smile.
丘を越えて 山を越えて 谷を越えてゆくんだ
Crossing hills, crossing mountains, crossing valleys...
川を越えて 海を越えて 空を越えてゆくんだ
Crossing rivers, crossing seas, crossing skies...
雨上りの空 虹を描いて 皆に会いに行こうよ
Painting a rainbow in the post-rain sky, going to see everyone!
大切なのは 僕でいること 間違いだらけの毎日も
What's important is being myself, even in days full of mistakes.
手と手をつないで 目と目を合わせて どこまでも歩こう
Holding hands, locking eyes, let's walk on forever!
全然つかえないきみのこと
I don't get you at all...
全然知らないうちに
Before I even knew it,
ココロ奪われるなんてこと
you stole my heart?
あるはずないでしょ
That can't possibly be true!
それは無愛想な笑顔だったり
Was it that unfriendly smile?
それは日曜日の日暮れだったり
Or Sunday's twilight hour?
それはテストばっかの期間だったり
Or exam prep season?
それはきみという名のメランコリックニスト
Or you, the melancholic specialist?
手当たり次第強気でぶつかっても
Even if I bravely charge ahead blindly,
なににも手には残らないとと思い込んでる
I convince myself nothing will remain.
ちょっとくらいの勇気だだってちっちゃくなって塞ぎ込んでる
With just a little courage, I shrink away...
わたしだから
'Cuz that's just who I am!
全然つかえないきみのこと
I don't get you at all...
全然知らないうちに
Before I even knew it,
ココロ奪おととしていたのは
trying to steal your heart
わたしのほうだもん
was actually me all along!
全然つかえないきみのこと
I don't get you at all...
全然知らないうちに
Before I even knew it,
ココロ奪われるなんてこと
you stole my heart?
あるはずないでしょ
That can't possibly be true!
全然気づかないきみなんて
You don't notice me at all
全然知らない知らないもんね
and you don't know a thing!
「ねえねえ」じゃないわよ
Don't you give me that "Hey, hey!"
この笑顔をまだ眠れないでしょ
I'll be losing sleep tonight again!
みんな今日はみせてくれてありがとう
Thank you all for showing me today!
これからもよろしくね
Please keep taking care of me!
星占いも同じわたしが見るのかな
Same horoscope... is that what I'm seeing?
無口で生真面目 そんな可愛くないやつ
An uncommunicative, earnest, uncute guy...
あの夢にきみが出で来たときから
Ever since you appeared in my dream,
素直じゃないんだって
I haven't been honest with myself!
すなおじゃないの
I'm just not being honest!
「ねえねえ」だってつかえないきみのこと
"Hey, hey!" I still don't get you at all
全然知らないうちに
Before I even knew it
ココロ奪おうとしていたのは
trying to steal your heart
私のほうだもん
was actually me all along!
ななな のらな のらら のらな のららら
(La la la...)
そういう時期なのかな こぼれた恋のいとしのメランコリック
Is this love's precious melancholic phase?
いとしのメランコリック
My precious melancholic...
すなおじゃないの
I'm just not being honest!
おいでファンタジー 好きさミステリー
Come to fantasy, love the mystery
君の若さ隠さないで
Don't hide your youth!
不思議したくて 冒険したくて 誰もしんなウズウズしてる
Wanting wonder, wanting adventure, everyone's itching for it!
おいで ファンタジー
Come on, fantasy,
好きさ ミステリー
loved mystery,
君の若さ 隠さないで
don't hide your youth.
不思議にしたくて 冒険したくて
Wanting things mysterious, wanting adventures,
誰もしも ウズウズしてる
everyone is itching for it.
大人のフリして 諦めたりしちゃ
If you pretend to be an adult and give up,
奇跡の謎など 解けないよ
you can't solve the mysteries of miracles.
もっとワイルドに もっとたくましく
Live more wildly, more strongly,
生きてごらん
live your life.
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance,
I'll give you romance.
ホントの勇気 見せてくれたら
If you show me your true courage,
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance,
I'll give you romance.
トキメク胸に キラキラ光った
In your throbbing heart, a sparkling, shining
夢をあげるよ
dream I'll give to you.
いつかワンダフル
Someday wonderful,
きっとビューティフル
surely beautiful,
人のジャングル 迷い込んで
getting lost in the human jungle.
スリルしたくて 幸せしたくて
Wanting thrills, wanting happiness,
何故かみんな ソワソワしてる
somehow everyone is restless.
思ったとおりに 叫ばなくちゃ
If you don't shout just as you think,
願いは空まで 届かない
your wish won't reach the sky.
もっとセクシーに もっと美しく
Live more sexier, more beautifully,
生きてごらん
live your life.
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance,
I'll give you romance.
ホントの涙 見せてくれたら
If you show me your true tears,
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance,
I'll give you romance.
淋しい心 やさしく包んで
Gently wrapping your lonely heart,
愛をあげるよ
I'll give you love.
スリルしたくて
Wanting thrills,
幸せしたくて
wanting happiness,
何故かみんな ソワソワしてる
somehow everyone is restless.
思ったとおりに 叫ばなくちゃ
If you don't shout just as you think,
願いは空まで 届かない
your wish won't reach the sky.
もっとセクシーに もっと美しく 生きてごらん
Live more sexier, more beautifully, live your life.
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance,
I'll give you romance.
ホントの涙 見せてくれたら
If you show me your true tears,
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance,
I'll give you romance.
淋しい心 やさしく包んで
Gently wrapping your lonely heart,
愛をあげるよ
I'll give you love.
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance,
I'll give you romance.
ホントの勇気 見せてくれたら
If you show me your true courage,
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance,
I'll give you romance.
トキメク胸に キラキラ光った
In your throbbing heart, a sparkling, shining
夢をあげるよ
dream I'll give to you.
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance,
I'll give you romance.
ホントの勇気 見せてくれたら
If you show me your true courage,
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance,
I'll give you romance.
トキメク胸に キラキラ光った
In your throbbing heart, a sparkling, shining
夢をあげるよ
dream I'll give to you.
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance,
I'll give you romance.
ホントの勇気 見せてくれたら
If you show me your true courage,
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance,
I'll give you romance.
トキメク胸に キラキラ光った
In your throbbing heart, a sparkling, shining
夢をあげるよ
dream I'll give to you.
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance,
I'll give you romance.
ホントの勇気 見せてくれたら
If you show me your true courage,
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance,
I'll give you romance.
トキメク胸に キラキラ光った
In your throbbing heart, a sparkling, shining
夢をあげるよ
dream I'll give to you.
Catch You Catch Me 作詞・作曲：広瀬香美
[Song: Catch You Catch Me]
会いたいな 会えないな
I miss you, can't see you,
せつないな この気持ち
breaks my heart, this feeling.
言えないの 言いたいな
Can't tell you, really want to say it,
チャンス逃してばかり
I keep missing my chance.
だって だって 翼広げ二人で
Because see, spreading our wings together,
空をマラソン 夢をユニゾンしたい
do a marathon across the sky, unify our dreams.
ほら Catch You Catch You Catch Me Catch Me 待って
See? Catch you catch you catch me catch me, wait,
こっちを向いて スキだといって
look this way, say you love me.
そう Nice to Meet You Good to See You きっと
Yeah, nice to meet you, good to see you, definitely,
私の想い あなたのハートに飛んで飛んで飛んでいけ 迷わない
my feelings fly straight to your heart without hesitating!
たまにね なくなっちゃう 身体のバッテリー
Sometimes my body's battery runs out,
あなたの笑顔で いつも充電満タン
fully charged up by your smile always!
パワー爆発しちゃえ
Power exploding!
お願い お願い まずは友達から
Pretty please, let's start as friends first,
笑って 見つめて 楽しい毎日日にしたい
laugh, gaze, and make every day fun.
ほら Catch You Catch You Catch Me Catch Me ゼッタイ
See? Catch you catch you catch me catch me, absolutely,
運命だって お似合いだって
say it's destiny, we're a perfect match.
そう Nice to Meet You Good to See You きっと
Yeah, nice to meet you, good to see you, definitely,
誰にも負けない...
second to none...
会いたいな 会えないな せつないな この気持ち
I want to see you, but I can't... How sad, these feelings...
言えないな 言いたいのに チャンス逃してばかり
I can't say it, but I want to. I just keep letting my chance slip by.
だって だって 翼広げ二人で 空をマラソン 夢をユニゾンしたいの
But still, together, let's spread our wings and run across the sky to unite our dreams.
ほら Catch You Catch You Catch Me Catch Me 待って こっちを向いて スキだといって
Hey, Catch You Catch You Catch Me Catch Me, wait! Look this way and say you like me!
そう Nice to Meet You Good to See You きっと 私の想い あなたのハートに 飛んで飛んで飛んでいけ 迷わない
Yeah, Nice to Meet You Good to See You, surely my feelings will fly, fly, fly straight into your heart!
誰にも負けない あなたに世界で 一番一番一番一番コイシテル
I won't lose to anyone—you are number one, one, one, one in the world to me! I'm in love with you!
ほら Catch You Catch You Catch Me Catch Me 待って
Hey, Catch You Catch You Catch Me Catch Me, wait!
こっちを向いて スキだといって そう Nice to Meet You Good to See You きっと
Look this way and say you like me, yeah, Nice to Meet You Good to See You, surely...
私の想い あなたのハートに 飛んで飛んで飛んでいけ 迷わない
My feelings will fly, fly, fly straight into your heart without hesitation!
たまにね なくなっちゃう 身体のバッテリー
Sometimes my body's battery runs completely dry,
あなたの笑顔で いつも充電満タン パワー爆発しちゃう
but with your smile, it's fully charged and ready to explode!
お願い お願い まずはお友達から 笑って 見つめて 楽しい毎日にしたいの
Please, please, let's start as friends first, I want to smile, look at you, and have fun every day.
ほら Catch You Catch You Catch Me Catch Me ゼッタイ
Hey, Catch You Catch You Catch Me Catch Me, absolutely!
運命だって お似合いだって そう Nice to Meet You Good to See You きっと
It's destiny, it suits us well, yeah, Nice to Meet You Good to See You, surely...
誰にも負けない あなたに世界で 一番一番一番一番コイシテル
I won't lose to anyone—you are number one, one, one, one in the world to me! I'm in love with you!
わっ ちゅー げっ ちゅー 熱烈 うおん ちゅー
Whatcha getcha, passionate wantcha!
しゅき しゅぎて 弾けた vivid マインド
A vivid mind bursting with too much love!
ルーレット グッド スタート きっと ゲット 1等！1等！1等！
Roulette, good start, surely gonna get first place, first, first!
永久 センキュー ときめき knock you
Eternal thank you, a heart-throbbing knock you!
1ミリ の 隙間 に ダイビング
Diving right into a one-millimeter gap!
ラブ スタンプ 全部 コンプ 運勢 アップ
Love stamps, complete them all, luck goes up!
いい ぞ！いい ぞ！いい ぞ！いい ぞ！ せーの！
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go! Let's go! Ready, go!
だって 今日 は ゴッド メンタル 勇ましき チャレンジャー
Because today my mental is godly, a valiant challenger!
ちょっと だけ センチメンタル
Just a little bit sentimental,
だいしきゅーだいしゅきゅー ♡ 123 ハイ！ まみ むめ も め も 見れないの 立ちつてとてと 手と手 が 触れて
Dai-shiku dai-shiku ♡ 1, 2, 3, hey! Mamimumemo memo can't even look, tachitsutetote hand in hand touching!
だいしきゅーだいしゅき になれ！ もっと ぎゅぎゅぎゅっと 強制 ラブ！
Become my dai-shiku dai-shuki! Give me a tighter, tighter forced love!
あのね マリオネット 透けてる ハート でもね この胸 見透かさないで
You know, I'm a marionette with a see-through heart, but don't see right through my chest!
だいしきゅーだいしゅき になれ！ アタシじゃない なんて 終わってんね
Become my dai-shiku dai-shuki! Saying "it's not me" is so over!
わっ ちゅー げっ ちゅー 蜜月 うおん ちゅー
Whatcha getcha, honeymoon wantcha!
しゅき しゅぎて 空 ぶる cutie マインド ルーレット ちょっと ストップ 一旦 休憩
A cutie mind soaring too high on love, roulette, stop for a quick break!
いや！いや！いや！ でも！ せーの！ だって 今日 は 求める 麗しき チャレンジャー
No way, no way, but still—ready, go! Because today I'm seeking a gorgeous challenger,
ハート 描い た オートメーション だいしきゅーだいしゅきゅー ♡ 123 ハイ！
an automated heart drawn in love, dai-shiku dai-shiku ♡ 1, 2, 3, hey!
まみ むめろめろに して 欲しい の なに ぬ ねこねこ 恋 の コネクト
I want you to melt me completely, nani nu neko-neko, love's connect!
だいしきゅーだいしゅき になれ！ もっとき き き きっしゅ 強制 ラブ！
Become my dai-shiku dai-shuki! Give me a ki-ki-ki-kiss forced love!
あのね マリオネット あやつられでぃ でもね それもね 悪くはないで
You know, I'm a marionette being manipulated, but even that's not so bad!
だいしきゅーだいしゅき になれ！ アタシじゃない なんて 終わってんね
Become my dai-shiku dai-shuki! Saying "it's not me" is so over!
フレンディー な フリ し て 周波数 を 乱さ ない で
Acting all friendly, don't scramble my frequency!
いわくづき の 魅惑 の リップ リアル に なる be love
The charming lips of a cursed tale, becoming real in be love!
まみ むめ も め も 見れないの 立ちつてとてと 手と手 が 触れて
Mamimumemo memo can't even look, tachitsutetote hand in hand touching!
だいしきゅーだいしゅき になれ！ もっと ぎゅぎゅぎゅっと 強制 ラブ！
Become my dai-shiku dai-shuki! Give me a tighter, tighter forced love!
あのね クリオネ 透けてる ハート でもね この胸 見透かさないで
You know, I'm a clione with a see-through heart, but don't see right through my chest!
だいしきゅーだいしゅき になれ！ アタシじゃない なんて 終わってんね
Become my dai-shiku dai-shuki! Saying "it's not me" is so over!
まみ むめ も め も 見れないの 立ちつてとてと 手と手 が 触れて
Mamimumemo memo can't even look, tachitsutetote hand in hand touching!
だいしきゅーだいしゅき になれ！ もっと ぎゅぎゅぎゅっと 強制 ラブ！
Become my dai-shiku dai-shuki! Give me a tighter, tighter forced love!
あのね クリオネ 透けてる ハート でもね この胸 見透かさないで
You know, I'm a clione with a see-through heart, but don't see right through my chest!
だいしきゅーだいしゅき になれ！ アタシじゃない なんて 終わってんね
Become my dai-shiku dai-shuki! Saying "it's not me" is so over!
フレンディー な フリ し て 周波数 を 乱さ ない で
Acting all friendly, don't scramble my frequency!
いわくづき の 魅惑 の リップ リアル に なる be love
The charming lips of a cursed tale, becoming real in be love!
まみ むめ も め も 見れないの 立ちつてとてと 手と手 が 触れて
Mamimumemo memo can't even look, tachitsutetote hand in hand touching!
だいしきゅーだいしゅき になれ！ もっと ぎゅぎゅぎゅっと 強制 ラブ！
Become my dai-shiku dai-shuki! Give me a tighter, tighter forced love!
あのね クリオネ 透けてる ハート でもね この胸 見透かさないで
You know, I'm a clione with a see-through heart, but don't see right through my chest!
だいしきゅーだいしゅき になれ！ アタシじゃない なんて 終わってんね
Become my dai-shiku dai-shuki! Saying "it's not me" is so over!
だいしきゅーだいしゅき！
Daishikyu daishuki!
になれ！
Be mine!
きゅきゅきゅきゅきゅと強制LOVE！
Kyukyukyukyuku-Kyosei LOVE!
あのねくりおねつけてるハート
Even if you don't show it, hearts are attached.
でもねこの胸見つかさないで
Even so, don't miss this chest of mine.
だいしきゅーだいしゅき！
Daishikyu daishuki!
になれ！
Be mine!
あたしじゃないなんて終わってんね！
Saying "I don't need that" is already over!
あれ気づいちゃいましたか？
Did you notice already?
わたしの一番かわいいところ
My cutest part...
うまれて30秒で最初に聞いた言葉は
Thirty seconds since birth, the first words I heard...
さすがにそりゃ覚えてないけど嬉しかったはず
I probably don't remember, but I must've been happy.
でもでもだいたいのことは変わってないっていうかそりゃ
Even now, the important things haven't changed—
中身は変わっていますのでその辺でも評価！（おねがい！）
Well, the inside has changed, so how's that? (Please!)
携帯のアンテナを光らせて
Light up the antenna on your phone!
それが超キュートなあの頃だって知ってたって言うか
Knowing that was how super cute times were back then.
アンテナって何って言ってるようなわたしに付き合ってくれるの好き
Like, what even is an antenna? You're supposed to match mine!
逆にでも私のどこが好き？
Conversely, what do you like best about me?
ねえねえねえ！
Hey, hey, hey!
わたしの一番、かわいいところに気付いている
You've noticed my absolute cutest part.
そんな君が一番すごいすごいよすごすぎる！
You're such an amazingly, incredibly lucky person!
そして君が知ってるわたしが一番かわいいのわたしもそれに気付いた！
And you know that I'm the cutest one, and I've realized it too!
だからそれかわいい、あれかわいいなんて誰かわいい、それかわいいなんて言わないで、
So don't say things like "that's cute" or "this is cute" about anyone else!
わたし以外なんてやだなんてありえない？
No way, saying anyone other than me is out of the question!
わたし気付いちゃいました！
I've noticed already!
毎日何十秒、褒められまくったお菓子は
Every day for tens of seconds, being praised endlessly makes the snacks...
他よりちょっと甘くなるって前に聞いたような
Sweeter than usual, or so I heard before.
さすがにそれなんか変だけどわたしは言われたいタイプでして
That sounds a bit strange, but that's just the type of person I am!
もっとわかりやすくていいんだよ、お待たせしてます
More easily understandable, so look forward to it.
何してもどんな顔見せててもいつも超キュートだって確信してるのはなんだかさ知らなかったタイプの運命の人なのは
No matter what you do or what face you show, I'm confident you'll always be super cute.
わたしの一番、かわいいところをよく見てる
You've noticed my absolute cutest part.
そんな君がほんとに超ラッキーな人すぎる！
You're such an amazingly, incredibly lucky person!
そして君が何年たってもそう思えるようにわたしはそれに気付いた
And you know that I'm the cutest one, and I've realized it too!
会えないときもどんな表情してるかとか
If you can't meet me, I wonder what kind of expression you make.
気持ち悪いぐらい想像しちゃうから
You'll probably miss me about this much, right?
それかわいい、おれかわいいって本当にかわいいって言って！
So say it—you're so, so, so, so cute!
わたしの一番かわいいところに気付いてる
You've noticed my absolute cutest part.
そんな君が一番すごいすごいよすごすぎる！
You're such an amazingly, incredibly lucky person!
そして君が知ってるわたしが一番かわいいのわたしもそれに気付いた
And you know that I'm the cutest one, and I've realized it too!
わたしの一番、かわいいところをよく見てる
You've noticed my absolute cutest part.
そんな君がほんとに超ラッキーな人すぎる！
You're such an amazingly, incredibly lucky person!
そして君が何年たってもそう思えるようにわたしはそれに気付いた
And you know that I'm the cutest one, and I've realized it too!
わたしの一番、かわいいところに気付いてる
You've noticed my absolute cutest part.
そんな君が一番すごいすごいよすごすぎる！
You're such an amazingly, incredibly lucky person!
そして君が知ってるわたしが一番かわいいのわたしもそれに気付いた！
And you know that I'm the cutest one, and I've realized it too!
だからそれかわいい、あれかわいいなんて誰かわいい、それかわいいなんて言わないで、
So don't say things like "that's cute" or "this is cute" about anyone else!
わたし以外なんてやだなんてありえない？
No way, saying anyone other than me is out of the question!
今日はもう引返そうかな
Should we turn back for today?
あしたはもっといけるかな
I wonder if tomorrow will go better.
きしむ
Creaking...
見つけたい 遠く「うれしい」を多く
Wanting to find so many distant "I'm happy"s,
きらり光るホープ 動く、動く
Brightly glittering hope, moving, moving!
とりとめのないトーク どこまでも続く
Unstoppable talk continuing on endlessly,
さようなら孤独 動く、動く
So farewell, loneliness, moving, moving!
難解なパズルを解くように
Like solving a complex puzzle,
きっと何度も「知りたい」を知るから
Surely, again and again, we'll learn what we want to know!
だから 1 2 3 で歩き出せ
So in 1, 2, 3: start walking!
今日も あしたも きのうも 変わらない
Today, tomorrow or yesterday, it doesn't change.
ならば 1 2 3 で歩き出せ
Then with 1, 2, 3: start walking!
回る世界と逆向きで
Facing the opposite direction of this revolving world.
そうさ 1 2 3 で踊りだせ
Yeah, with 1, 2, 3: start dancing!
今日も あしたも きのうも 忘れたい
We want to forget today, tomorrow and yesterday.
ならば 1 2 3 で動き出せ
Then with 1, 2, 3: start moving!
きっとそれが a-a-a-a- answer さ
Surely, that's the a-a-a-a- answer!
今日はもう引返そうかな
Should we turn back for today?
あしたはもっといけるかな
I wonder if tomorrow will go better.
きしむ
Creaking...
見つけたい 遠く「うれしい」を多く
Wanting to find so many distant "I'm happy"s,
きらり光るホープ 動く、動く
Brightly glittering hope, moving, moving!
とりとめのないトーク どこまでも続く
Unstoppable talk continuing on endlessly,
さようなら孤独 動く、動く
So farewell, loneliness, moving, moving!
難解なパズルを解くように
Like solving a complex puzzle,
きっと何度も「知りたい」を知るから
Surely, again and again, we'll learn what we want to know!
だから 1 2 3 で歩き出せ
So in 1, 2, 3: start walking!
今日も あしたも きのうも 変わらない
Today, tomorrow or yesterday, it doesn't change.
ならば 1 2 3 で歩き出せ
Then with 1, 2, 3: start walking!
回る世界と逆向きで
Facing the opposite direction of this revolving world.
そうさ 1 2 3 で踊りだせ
Yeah, with 1, 2, 3: start dancing!
今日も あしたも きのうも 忘れたい
We want to forget today, tomorrow and yesterday.
ならば 1 2 3 で動き出せ
Then with 1, 2, 3: start moving!
きっとそれが a-a-a-a- answer さ
Surely, that's the a-a-a-a- answer!
今日はもう引返そうかな
Should we turn back for today?
あしたはもっといけるかな
I wonder if tomorrow will go better.
きしむ
Creaking...
見つけたい 遠く「うれしい」を多く
Wanting to find so many distant "I'm happy"s,
きらり光るホープ 動く、動く
Brightly glittering hope, moving, moving!
とりとめのないトーク どこまでも続く
Unstoppable talk continuing on endlessly,
さようなら孤独 動く、動く
So farewell, loneliness, moving, moving!
難解なパズルを解くように
Like solving a complex puzzle,
きっと何度も「知りたい」を知るから
Surely, again and again, we'll learn what we want to know!
だから 1 2 3 で歩き出せ
So in 1, 2, 3: start walking!
今日も あしたも きのうも 変わらない
Today, tomorrow or yesterday, it doesn't change.
ならば 1 2 3 で歩き出せ
Then with 1, 2, 3: start walking!
回る世界と逆向きで
Facing the opposite direction of this revolving world.
そうさ 1 2 3 で踊りだせ
Yeah, with 1, 2, 3: start dancing!
今日も あしたも きのうも 忘れたい
We want to forget today, tomorrow and yesterday.
ならば 1 2 3 で動き出せ
Then with 1, 2, 3: start moving!
きっとそれが a-a-a-a- answer さ
Surely, that's the a-a-a-a- answer!
だから 1 2 3 で歩き出せ
So in 1, 2, 3: start walking!
今日も あしたも きのうも 変わらない
Today, tomorrow or yesterday, it doesn't change.
ならば 1 2 3 で歩き出せ
Then with 1, 2, 3: start walking!
回る世界と逆向きで
Facing the opposite direction of this revolving world.
そうさ 1 2 3 で踊りだせ
Yeah, with 1, 2, 3: start dancing!
今日も あしたも きのうも 忘れたい
We want to forget today, tomorrow and yesterday.
ならば 1 2 3 で動き出せ
Then with 1, 2, 3: start moving!
きっとそれが a-a-a-a- answer さ
Surely, that's the a-a-a-a- answer!
だから 1 2 3 で歩き出せ
So in 1, 2, 3: start walking!
今日も あしたも きのうも 変わらない
Today, tomorrow or yesterday, it doesn't change.
ならば 1 2 3 で歩き出せ
Then with 1, 2, 3: start walking!
うわーっ！
Ah!
おい、やばいって！ライブまであと…
Hey, this is bad! Only...
言う暇ないのら！
There's no time!
ほ、ライブ！
H-Hurry up!
早く起きろ！今頃みんな待ってんだ！
Quick, hurry up and get out here! Everyone's waiting!
靴下はかして欲しいのら。
But I wanted you to brush my costume for me...
自分ではきなさい！
Put them on yourself!
あと1時間待って。
Give me another hour.
待てるか！ちよこそんなに化粧しなくても可愛いだろ！
Wait, you've got plenty of time! You're cute even without putting on makeup!
こっちは準備できたよ。
I'm all set over here.
荷物全部置いとけ！乗れ！
Load all of that in! Get in!
この車はボタンちゃんなのら？
Is this car named after Botan-chan?
いや違うけど、なんだこのデカいスイッチ？
No, different, but what's this huge switch?
「押しちゃダメ」って書いてあるけど。
It says "Do not press," though.
じゃあ押してみよう。
Then let's press it.
なんで？
Why?
え？
Huh?
ここどこ？
Where's this?
あれ、恐竜じゃないのら？
Wait, isn't that a dinosaur?
本当だー！
Seriously!
うわあ！食われる食われる！
Whoa, we're gonna get eaten!
恐竜ってまだ生きていたのらね！
Dinosaurs were actually still alive, then!
これタイムスリップしてるって！
This is time-slipping!
てか恐竜買ってみたい。
I kinda want to buy a dinosaur.
あなたは飛べるやつがいい。
You're the kind of person who could fly.
にしてもお腹すいてるのらね！たこ焼き食べる？
Even so, it looks pretty hungry, doesn't it? Wanna feed it takoyaki?
お前、口はお前なのだったがよ！
Oh, wait...
何がてぬくれでんこぬら！
What a careless-donkou.
ボタン、早くスイッチ押して！
Botan, hit the switch quickly!
でも押しちゃダメって書いてあるし。
It says we shouldn't press it though.
最初に押したのお前だろがよ！ちょこせよ押して！
You're the one who pressed it first! Hurry up and press it!
セクシーな感じで？
Does it feel sexy?
いや、普通に。
No, normally.
ポチッとな…
Like this...
すごーい！月がきれいなのら！
It's huge! The moon is so clear, too!
ねえ、みなみ…
Hey, Minami...
みんな何やってるのら？
What are you all doing?
えっ、これを押してほしいの？
Hey, do you want to press this?
うわ！
Whoa!
なんとか時間に間に合った。
We somehow made it in time.
あなたたちは気づいてしまったのら！今まさにあなたたちはタイムスリップをしていたのらー！
You realized it just now? Right now, you guys were time-slipping!
そうだな。
True.
ところで、この恐竜どうする？森2階す？
By the way, what do we do about this dinosaur? Forest, second-floor...
なんらかの方に触れそう。
We should probably touch base with Houki.
たぶんこのスイッチを押すとタイムスリップする仕組みなのら。
I bet if we press this switch, it triggers a time-slip mechanism.
いいからライブ会場に向かおう！
Anyway, let's head to the live venue!
Moonlight Merry-Go-Round
Candy-Go-Round Ready-Go-“Live”
夢のようなスピードでエスコート
Escorting with a dream-like speed,
時の流れはいつでもゆっくり
The flow of time is always leisurely.
キミのclap-clap-clap
Clap-clap-clap with you,
(everybody clap hands up)
空想へドライブ★
Driving into daydreams★
Moonlight Merry-Go-Round
Candy-Go-Round Parallel-World
始まりのベルが鳴り響く夜に
The bell of beginnings echoes into the night,
迎えに行くから
Going out to greet you.
同じビートでひとつのナンバー
Playing a single number to the same beat,
奏でよう
Let's play it out.
ハートを1ミリでも動かせば
Even if you move your heart by just a millimeter,
キセキ起こす大きな1歩につながるから
It leads to a huge first step that works miracles.
つまらないときは「わくわく」をクリックしてみよう
When you're bored, try clicking on "Excitement,"
キミとdance×dance×dance
Dance × dance × dance with you,
(everybody shall we dance?)
ステップ踏んでパーティーしよう！
Let's stamp our feet and have a party!
Stand up Ring-a-bell Fairy-tail Wonderland-“Live”
出掛けたい場所へ連れてくよ
Take me to the place I want to go.
瞳閉ざしたら合図なんだ
Closing our eyes is the signal.
幻想トリックもう止められない
Fantasy-trip, we can't stop it anymore.
Start line Ring-a-bell Fairy-tail Colorful-night
Start-line, Ring-a-bell, Fairy-tail, Colorful-night,
どんな距離だって越えて会いにいく
Crossing any distance to go meet you,
夜空を見上げて
Looking up at the night sky,
ドラマチックで忘れられない今にしよう
Let's make it an unforgettable, dramatic present.
起きてても覚めない魔法かけるから
Casting a spell that won't fade even when you wake up,
はじめようステージを
Let the show begin!
キミの胸のドキドキ
With your heart going doki-doki,
嘘じゃないよリアルだよ
It's not a lie, it's totally real!
星もうれしくて飛び回ってるよ
Even the stars are happily flying around.
リズムを合わせるように
Just like matching the rhythm,
とびきりな夢を
With a thrilling dream,
キミとキミとキミとキミとキミと一緒に
Together with you, you, you, you, you, you!
Moonlight Merry-Go-Round
Candy-Go-Round Ready-Go-“Live”
夢のようなスピードでエスコート
Escorting with a dream-like speed,
歌に乗り込めば行けるんだ
We can go if we ride on the song!
タイムスリップもう止められない
Time-slip, we can't stop it anymore!
Moonlight Merry-Go-Round
Candy-Go-Round Parallel-World
始まりのベルが鳴り響く夜に
The bell of beginnings echoes into the night,
迎えに行くから
Going out to greet you.
同じビートでひとつのナンバー
Playing a single number to the same beat,
奏でよう
Let's play it out.
ハートを1ミリでも動かせば
Even if you move your heart by just a millimeter,
キセキ起こす大きな1歩につながるから
It leads to a huge first step that works miracles.
つまらないときは「わくわく」をクリックしてみよう
When you're bored, try clicking on "Excitement,"
キミとdance×dance×dance
Dance × dance × dance with you,
ステップ踏んでパーティーしよう！
Let's stamp our feet and have a party!
Stand up Ring-a-bell Fairy-tail Wonderland-“Live”
出掛けたい場所へ連れてくよ
Take me to the place I want to go.
連れてくよ
I'll take you there!
瞳閉じたら 合図なんだ
Closing our eyes is the signal.
妄想トリップ もう止められない
This delusion trip can't be stopped anymore!
Start line ring-a-bell fairy-tail
Start line, ring-a-bell, fairy tail,
colorful-night どんな距離だって
colorful night! No matter the distance,
越えて会いにいく
I'll cross it to go meet you.
夜空を見上げて
Looking up at the night sky,
ドラマチックで忘れない
it's dramatic and unforgettable.
今にしよう
Let's make it the present!
起きてても覚めない魔法かけるから
I'll cast a spell that won't fade even awake.
始めようステージを
Let's start the stage!
キミの胸のドキドキ
The pounding in your chest—
ウソじゃないよ リアルだよ
it's no lie, it's real!
星もうれしくて飛び回ってるよ
Even the stars are happily flying around.
リズムを合わせるように
To match the rhythm,
飛びきりな夢を
let's spin an extraordinary dream...
キミとキミとキミとキミとキミと一緒に
Together with you, you, you, you, and you!
Moonlight merry-go-round candy-go-round
夢のようなスピードで飛び立とう
let's take off at a dreamlike speed!
歌に乗り込めば行けるんだ
We can go if we ride on the song.
タイムスリップもう止められない
Time slip can't be stopped anymore!
Starlight merry-go-round candy-go-round parallel-world
Starlight, merry-go-round, candy-go-round, parallel world!
はじまりのベルが鳴り響く夜に
Into the night when the starting bell rings out,
迎えに行くから
I'm coming to pick you up.
同じビートでひとつのナンバー
Playing a single tune with the same beat,
奏でよう
let's play it together!
朝目覚めて 真っ先に思い浮かべる 君のこと
Waking up in the morning, the first thing on my mind is you.
思い切って 前髪を切った
I made up my mind and cut my bangs.
「どうしたの？」って 聞かれたくて
I wanted you to ask, "What's with the new look?" and smile at me.
ピンクのスカート お花の髪飾り
A light pink skirt, flower hair ornaments—
さして出かけるの 今日の私はかわいいのよ！
I'm stepping out today looking super cute!
メルト 溶けてしまいそう
Melt! I feel like I'm melting away.
好きだなんて 絶対言えない……
I can never, ever say "I like you"......
メルト 目も合わせられない
Melt! I can't even look you in the eye.
恋に恋なんてしないわ わたし だって君のことが……好きなの
I'm not just in love with love—it's because I love you...
天気予報がウソをついた
The weather forecast told a lie—
土砂降りの雨が降る
a torrential rain is pouring down.
カバンに入れたままの オルタッタ傘うれしくない ため息をついた
My foldable umbrella left in my bag doesn't bring joy, just a sigh.
そんなとき 「しょうがないから入ってやるよ」なんて
That's when you smiled beside me, saying, "Guess I have to share mine."
隣にいるきみが笑う 恋に落ちる音がした
I heard the sound of my heart falling in love.
メルト 息が詰まりそう
Melt! It feels like I'm losing my breath.
君に触れてる右手蹟が震える
My right hand touching you is trembling.
高鳴る胸はんばん この傘 手を伸ばせば届く距離 どうしよう……！
My pounding heart... so close our hands could touch. What should I do...?!
想いよ 届け 君に お願い時間を止めて 泣きそうなの
Reach my feelings, please stop time—I'm about to cry from pure joy!
メルト 駅に着いてしまう…… もう会えない 近くて遠いよ だから
Melt! We're reaching the station... parting soon, so close yet so far.
メルト 手をつないで歩きたい！ もうバイバイしなくちゃいけないの？ 今すぐわたしを抱きしめて！ なんてね
Melt! I want to hold hands and walk! Do we really have to say goodbye now? Hold me tight right now! ...Just kidding.
ピュアな恋に付いてしまった
I've fallen into a pure love,
Oh my! いい子じゃなくて
Oh my! Not being a good girl,
遠いよだから
it's far away, so...
捨てて手をつないで歩きたい
I want to cast off everything, hold hands and walk.
もう一回行きたい秘密のチョイスじゃないの
I want to go once more, isn't it a secret choice?
今すぐ私を抱きしめてなんてね
Hug me right now, just kidding.
どうもー！おはルーナ！
Hello everyone! Ohaluna!
ここまでの歌、みんな聞いてどうだったかな？
How did you all like the songs so far?
今回は可愛い歌を中心にライブさせてもらったのなよ！
This time, the live centered around cute songs, nano yo!
かりゅう、ねねちゃん、おまねちゃん、そしてすばちゃん、こぉらたん、一緒に歌ってくれてありがとー！
Karyu, Nene-chan, Omane-chan, Subaru-chan, and Koratan, thank you so much for singing with me!
そして今回もなんとね、演出がぽよにたくさんたくさん、ずっとね支えてもらったのな！ぽよ、本当に本当にありがとー！
And this time too, Poyo helped and supported me so much with the production! Poyo, thank you so, so much!
ルーナイトもいつもね、あなたのそばにいてくれてありがとー！
And Lunaites, thank you for always being by my side!
そして、このあとは、お知らせが2個あります！
And now, I have two announcements!
1つ目は、誕生日グッズが出るのなよ！ででん！
First, my birthday goods are coming out! Tada!
もう可愛さがね、あふれている！
The cuteness is just overflowing!
まずはね、1つ目は、こちら！
First of all, the first item is right here!
ルーナイトパーカー！
The Lunaite Hoodie!
なんとこちらね、ルーナイトのワンポイントと背中にはルーナイトの紋章がプリントされているなら、インナーカラーはね、うなたんカラーのピンクで腰られております！
It features a Lunaite emblem on the front and back, and the inner hood is lined in Unatan's signature pink color!
そして、2つ目は、こちら！ででん！可愛い！
And the second item is right here! Tada! So cute!
うなたんのワンピースのぬいぐるみ！約30cmあるボブヘアワンピースのぬいぐるみなら、こちらのポンチョもね取り外しすことができるようになっています！
It's a Unatan plushie in her blue dress version! Measuring about 30cm, the bob-hair dress plushie now has a removable poncho as well!
そして7月にね、新商品をお披露目したときに同じサイズのルーナイトのぬいぐるみも販売したので、一緒に並べて可愛がってほしいな！
And since we sold the same-sized Lunaite plushie when we announced the new goods in July, I hope you'll display them side by side!
そして、3つ目！
And the third item!
ルーナイト証明書！
The Lunaite Certificate!
もうこれがあれば、あなたは立派なルーナイトの証を手に入れることができます！表と裏に可愛いルーナイトとうなたんのイラストをね、描いてもらいました！
With this, you can officially prove you're a proud Lunaite! Both the front and back feature adorable illustrations of Lunaite and Unatan drawn for us!
シリアルナンバーもね、なんと印字されているので、ぜひぜひルーナイトのみんなにはこの証を肌身離さず持っていってほしいな！
It even has your unique serial number printed on it, so I really want all my Lunaites to keep this certificate close to you always!
以上ね、3点フルセット購入の方全員に直筆サイン＆押し複製メッセージ入りポストカードがついてきます！
For everyone who purchases the complete 3-item set, you'll receive a postcard with my handwritten signature and a duplicate message!
誕生日記念にぜひ、ルーナイトパーカーや証明書、うなたんのぬいぐるみをおうちにつれてってなのな！
For my birthday, please bring the Lunaite hoodie, certificate, and Unatan plushie home with you, nano na!
そして、お知らせ2個目は、なんと！オリジナル曲第3弾がこのあと21時からMV公開されます！
And the second announcement is... the MV for my 3rd original song will premiere tonight at 21:00!
そして、24時からは各種音楽サイトでリリースもされるなら！
And starting at 24:00, it will also be released on various music streaming sites!
ではね、最後にオリジナル新曲をお披露目します！聞いてください。「まんなかちてん」
Now then, finally, I'll be premiering my new original song! Please listen to 'Mannaka-Chiten'.
まんなかに かさなる ちてん
The point where the center overlaps,
まんなかで よくばる ちてん
the point of greed in the center,
まんなかの まんなか ちてん
the very center of the center,
「普通」のまま「特別」との間
between remaining 'ordinary' and 'special',
特別なときどき 普通の子みたいに
like an ordinary girl at special times.
まんなかちてん
Mannaka-chiten.
いつもおとぎ話のお姫様 みんなの輝くお月様 今日はおやすみして
Always the princess of fairy tales, everyone's shining moon, take a good night rest today...
重たい王冠 今はおいといて
Heavy crown, leave it aside for now,
どっちの私 も好きになってくれますか
Will you come to love whichever me I am?
どっちもほしいから まんなかにいたくなる
Because I want both, I want to be right in the middle.
スニーカーとシャツに着替えて あるき出したんだ
I changed into sneakers and a shirt and started walking out.
出発のアラームは新しい私が鳴らしてあげる
I'll have the new me ring the departure alarm.
両腕をいっぱいにしても ぎゅっとしたい この気持ち入んない
Even with both arms full, this tight feeling won't fit!
かたっぽなんて選べない 迷ってるなら まんなかなんだよ
You can't choose just one half; if you're hesitating, it's right in the middle!
まんなかに かさなる ちてん (てんてん ち てん)
The point where they overlap in the middle (ten-ten chi-ten)
まんなかで よくばる ちてん
The point of being greedy right in the middle
まんなかの まんなか ちてん (てんてん ち てん)
The very center of the middle point (ten-ten chi-ten)
ダイヤモンドとガラスのきらめき
The sparkle of diamonds and glass
薬指は二本ともくるっ 包みます
I wrap both ring fingers up snugly
1日2回のスイーツタイム (もぐもぐ～)
Sweets time twice a day (mogu-mogu~)
私2倍我慢できない (ぱくぱく～)
I can't hold back twice as much (paku-paku~)
わがままな魔法にかかっちゃった 境界超えたくなっちゃった
I got caught in a selfish magic, I wanted to cross the boundary
不意などきどきがゆうしゃのまえにあらわれる
Unexpected heartbeats appear before the hero
バレちゃいそうな伏線 かわいいでちゃう
Foreshadowing that's about to be exposed, pure cuteness comes out
いつの日か 来ると信じてた 白馬の王子様
The prince on a white horse I believed would come someday
自分だけでDuet 自由をGet 自転車でJet 迎えにいってあげます
Duet all by myself, get freedom, jet on a bicycle, I'll go meet you
1日48時間 2倍好きになっちゃったりして
48 hours a day, maybe falling in love twice as much
等身大も背伸びしても 一瞬で気づいてくれるのかな
Whether true to life or standing on tiptoe, will you notice in an instant?
まんなかに かさなる ちてん (てんてん ち てん)
The point where they overlap in the middle (ten-ten chi-ten)
まんなかで よくばる ちてん
The point of being greedy right in the middle
まんなかの まんなか ちてん (てんてん ち てん)
The very center of the middle point (ten-ten chi-ten)
誰も知らない 月と太陽のハーモニー
The harmony of the moon and sun that nobody knows
ダブル観測できるとこ見つけませんか まんかいの青春
Why not find a place for double observation? Full-bloom youth
満腹に摂取 まんてん流星群
Ingested to full stomach, a perfect meteor shower
満月 in heaven まんめん笑顔にして 満点すぎる思い出 まんまるなHappy day!!
Full moon in heaven, making a smiling face, overly perfect memories, a perfectly round happy day!!
せかいのまんなかで プリンセスを忘れるくらい 胸まんたんにきゅんってしてみたい
In the center of the world, I want to make my chest burst with cuteness enough to forget I'm a princess.
どっちだってホントの私 瞬きしたら君のどまんなか
Even you, the real me, right in the center of you if you blink
まんなかに かさなる ちてん (てんてん ち てん)
The point where they overlap in the middle (ten-ten chi-ten)
まんなかで よくばる ちてん
The point of being greedy right in the middle
まんなかの まんなか ちてん (てんてん ち てん)
The very center of the middle point (ten-ten chi-ten)
恋する女の子のいいとこ取りで
Taking the best parts of a girl in love
照れ隠しと素直の今まんなかちてん
The exact middle point of bashfulness and honesty right now
今年もたんじょう日をルーナイトと一緒に迎えられて最高に幸せなのら♪
アイラブぅ～♡ちゅぱ♡